Class of 1910 Records, 1906-1984
Smith College Archives
Class of 1910 Records
1906-1984
Smith College. Class of 1910.
RG 80 UUID:498e8d9e-e018-4216-b784-9537270a63f8
25 boxes (18.5 linear ft.)
Smith College Archives Northampton, MA
This collection is in 25 boxes and contains photographs, invitations, songs, newspaper clippings, and other memorabilia from the commencement and reunions of the Class of 1910.
The Class of 1910 was the thirty-second entering class and the thirty-second graduating class of Smith College.
The Class of 1910 records, 1906-1984, contain materials describing the history and activities of the Class of 1910, including materials from commencement, reunions, senior dramatics, and other important events. Types of materials include photographs, invitations, songs, newspaper clippings, questionnaires, treasury information, and other memorabilia.
Individual biographical files are also available, and often include photographs, photo albums, newspaper clippings, letters and correspondences, and class notes.
Information on Use
Terms of Access and Use
The records are open for research according to the regulations of the Smith College Archives without any additional restrictions.
History of the Collection
The Class of 1910 Records were created by the students and donated to the College Archives.
- Baccalaureate Service 1910 (Box 1758, Folder 1)
- Class Letters 1919-1984 (Box 1758, Folder 2)
- Class Secretary 1906-1980 (Box 1758, Folder 3)
- Commencement 1910 (Box 1758, Folder 4)
- Commencement Music 1910 (Box 1758, Folder 5)
- Commencement Photographs 1910 (Box 1758, Folder 6)
- Freshman Grind by 1909 1906 (Box 1758, Folder 7)
- Freshman Handbook 1906-1907 (Box 1758, Folder 8)
- Groups 1906-1910 (Box 1758, Folder 9)
- Group; Bacon Bat 1910 (Box 1758, Folder 10)
- History 1906-1910 (Box 1758, Folder 11)
- Ivy Day 1910 (Box 1758, Folder 12)
- Ivy Day Photographs 1910 (Box 1758, Folder 13)
- Junior Prom 1909 (Box 1758, Folder 14)
- Junior Ushers 1909 (Box 1758, Folder 15)
- Senior Dramatics 1910 (Box 1759, Folder 1)
- Senior Dramatics- Photographs 1910 (Box 1759, Folder 2)
- Songs undated (Box 1759, Folder 3)
- Class Supper 1910 (Box 1759, Folder 4)
- Sophomore Reception 1908 (Box 1759, Folder 5)
- Treasurer's Records- Ledger Book 1906-1970 (Box 1759, Folder 6)
- Treasurer's Records- Ledger Book 1916-1970 (Box 1759, Folder 7)
- Treasurer's Records- Reports 1935-1966 (Box 1759, Folder 8)
- Reunions undated (Box 1760, Folder 1)
- Reunions 1911 (Box 1760, Folder 2)
- Reunions 1915 (Box 1760, Folder 3)
- Reunions 1920 (Box 1760, Folder 4)
- Reunions 1920 (Box 1760, Folder 5)
- Reunions: Questionnaire 1920 (Box 1760, Folder 6)
- Reunions 1925 (Box 1760, Folder 7)
- Reunions 1930 (Box 1761, Folder 1)
- Reunions 1635 (Box 1761, Folder 2)
- Reunions 1940-1950 (Box 1761, Folder 3)
- Reunions 1955 (Box 1761, Folder 4)
- Reunions: Questionnaires A-C 1955 (Box 1761, Folder 5)
- Reunions: Questionnaires D-L 1955 (Box 1761, Folder 6)
- Reunions: Questionnaires M-R 1955 (Box 1761, Folder 7)
- Reunions: Questionnaires S-Z 1955 (Box 1761, Folder 8)
- Reunions 1960 (Box 1761, Folder 9)
- Reunions 1965 (Box 1761, Folder 10)
- Reunions 1970 (Box 1761, Folder 11)
- Reunions 1975 (Box 1761, Folder 12)
- Reunions 1980 (Box 1761, Folder 13)
- Reunion Songs undated (Box 1761, Folder 14)
- Banner (Box OV)